(this.webpackJsonpquiz=this.webpackJsonpquiz||[]).push([[0],{14:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(26)},19:function(e,t,n){},20:function(e,t,n){},26:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),r=n.n(a),o=n(11),i=n.n(o),c=(n(19),n(20),n(2)),s=n(3),l=n(5),u=n(4),m=n(8),d=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(e){var a;return Object(c.a)(this,n),(a=t.call(this,e)).state={style:null},a}return Object(s.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;setTimeout((function(){var t=e.props.done,n={opacity:1,width:"".concat(t,"%")};e.setState({style:n})}),2e3);var t=this.state.style,n=this.props.done;return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-bar",style:t},n,"%")))}}]),n}(a.Component),h=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(e){var a;return Object(c.a)(this,n),(a=t.call(this,e)).state={styleSuc:null,styleRig:null,styleWro:null,right:0,wrong:0,done:0},a}return Object(s.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;setTimeout((function(){var t=e.props,n=t.correct,a=t.attempt,r=100*(n+t.remain)/20,o=100-100*n/20,i=100*n/a,c={opacity:1,textAlign:"right",width:"".concat(i,"%")},s={opacity:1,textAlign:"right",width:"".concat(r,"%")},l={opacity:1,textAlign:"right",width:"".concat(o,"%")};e.setState({styleSuc:c,styleRig:s,styleWro:l,right:r,wrong:o,done:i})}),2e3);var t=this.state,n=t.styleSuc,a=t.styleRig,o=t.styleWro,i=t.done,c=t.right,s=t.wrong;this.props.success;return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("div",{className:"bar"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-right",style:a},r.a.createElement("p",null,c,"%")),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-done",style:n},i,"%"),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"progress-wrong",style:o},r.a.createElement("p",null,s,"%"))))}}]),n}(a.Component),y=n(6),f=n(12),p=function(){return r.a.createElement(y.a,{icon:f.a})},g=n(13),w=function(){return r.a.createElement(y.a,{icon:g.a})},E=function(e){Object(l.a)(n,e);var t=Object(u.a)(n);function n(){var e;return Object(c.a)(this,n),(e=t.call(this)).state={current:0,next:1,success:null,unsuccess:null,rightAns:"",correct:0,wrong:0,progress:0,total:20,attempt:0},e}return Object(s.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this,t=function(t,n){t.target.value===n?e.setState({success:{background:"#145A32",color:"#fff",border:"#145A32"},correct:++e.state.correct,attempt:++e.state.attempt,remain:e.state.total-e.state.attempt}):e.setState({success:{background:"#145A32",color:"#fff",border:"#145A32"},unsuccess:{background:"#A93226",color:"#fff",border:"#A93226"},wrong:++e.state.wrong,attempt:++e.state.attempt,remain:e.state.total-e.state.attempt})},n=this.state,a=n.current,o=n.next,i=n.success,c=n.unsuccess,s=n.progress,l=n.attempt,u=n.total,y=n.remain,f=n.correct,g=n.wrong;return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(d,{done:s}),r.a.createElement("div",null,m.slice(a,o).map((function(n,a){return r.a.createElement("div",{key:a,className:"quizPanel"},r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("h1",null,"Question ",l," of ",u," "),r.a.createElement("h2",null,decodeURIComponent(n.category)),"hard"===n.difficulty?r.a.createElement("div",{className:"iconStyle"},r.a.createElement(p,null),r.a.createElement(p,null),r.a.createElement(p,null),r.a.createElement(w,null),r.a.createElement(w,null)):"medium"===n.difficulty?r.a.createElement("div",{className:"iconStyle"},r.a.createElement(p,null),r.a.createElement(p,null),r.a.createElement(w,null),r.a.createElement(w,null),r.a.createElement(w,null)):r.a.createElement("div",{className:"iconStyle"},r.a.createElement(p,null),r.a.createElement(w,null),r.a.createElement(w,null),r.a.createElement(w,null),r.a.createElement(w,null))),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"quiz"},r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("h3",null,"Q: ",decodeURIComponent(n.question))),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"option"},r.a.createElement("button",{value:n.correct_answer,onClick:function(e){return t(e,n.correct_answer)},style:i},decodeURIComponent(n.correct_answer)),n.incorrect_answers.map((function(e){return r.a.createElement("button",{key:e,value:e,onClick:function(e){return t(e,n.correct_answer)},style:c},decodeURIComponent(e))})))),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"option"},r.a.createElement("button",{style:{backgroundColor:"#dec664"},onClick:function(){e.setState({current:e.state.next,next:e.state.next>=m.length?e.state.next:e.state.next+1,success:null,unsuccess:null,rightAns:"",progress:e.state.progress+5})}},"Next")))}))),100===s?r.a.createElement("div",{className:"quizPanel"},r.a.createElement("h2",null,"Total Questions are ",u,". You attempt ",l," Questions in which ",f," were right and ",g," were wrong answers.")):null,r.a.createElement(h,{correct:f,attempt:l,remain:y,a:!0}))}}]),n}(a.Component);var v=function(){return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},r.a.createElement(E,null))};Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));i.a.render(r.a.createElement(r.a.StrictMode,null,r.a.createElement(v,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))},8:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20hero%20in%20the%2080s%20animated%20video%20game%20%27Dragon%27s%20Lair%27%3F","correct_answer":"Dirk%20the%20Daring","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","Sir%20Toby%20Belch","Guy%20of%20Gisbourne"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20scientific%20name%20for%20modern%20day%20humans%3F","correct_answer":"Homo%20Sapiens","incorrect_answers":["Homo%20Ergaster","Homo%20Erectus","Homo%20Neanderthalensis"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Books","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20is%20Ron%20Weasley%27s%20middle%20name%3F","correct_answer":"Bilius","incorrect_answers":["Arthur","John","Dominic"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Comics","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Who%20is%20the%20creator%20of%20the%20comic%20series%20%22The%20Walking%20Dead%22%3F","correct_answer":"Robert%20Kirkman","incorrect_answers":["Stan%20Lee","Malcolm%20Wheeler-Nicholson","Robert%20Crumb"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Board%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"At%20the%20start%20of%20a%20standard%20game%20of%20the%20Monopoly%2C%20if%20you%20throw%20a%20double%20six%2C%20which%20square%20would%20you%20land%20on%3F","correct_answer":"Electric%20Company","incorrect_answers":["Water%20Works","Chance","Community%20Chest"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Jamaica%3F","correct_answer":"Kingston","incorrect_answers":["Rio%20de%20Janeiro","Dar%20es%20Salaam","Kano"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"When%20did%20Jamaica%20recieve%20its%20independence%20from%20England%3F%20","correct_answer":"1962","incorrect_answers":["1492","1963","1987"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kangaroos%20keep%20food%20in%20their%20pouches%20next%20to%20their%20children.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%202013%20how%20much%20money%20was%20lost%20by%20Nigerian%20scams%3F","correct_answer":"%2412.7%20Billion","incorrect_answers":["%2495%20Million","%24956%20Million","%242.7%20Billion"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"How%20old%20was%20Lyndon%20B.%20Johnson%20when%20he%20assumed%20the%20role%20of%20President%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F","correct_answer":"55","incorrect_answers":["50","60","54"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In%20World%20of%20Warcraft%20lore%2C%20who%20organized%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Paladins%3F","correct_answer":"Alonsus%20Faol","incorrect_answers":["Uther%20the%20Lightbringer","Alexandros%20Mograine","Sargeras%2C%20The%20Daemon%20Lord"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20the%20game%20%22Subnautica%22%2C%20a%20%22Cave%20Crawler%22%20will%20attack%20you.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20device%20that%20allows%20for%20infinite%20energy%20in%20the%20anime%20%22Dimension%20W%22%3F","correct_answer":"Coils","incorrect_answers":["Wires","Collectors","Tesla"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Cream%20the%20Rabbit%27s%20mom%20in%20the%20%22Sonic%20the%20Hedgehog%22%20series%3F","correct_answer":"Vanilla","incorrect_answers":["Peach","Strawberry","Mint"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"These%20two%20countries%20held%20a%20commonwealth%20from%20the%2016th%20to%2018th%20century.","correct_answer":"Poland%20and%20Lithuania","incorrect_answers":["Hutu%20and%20Rwanda","North%20Korea%20and%20South%20Korea","Bangladesh%20and%20Bhutan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which%20of%20these%20voices%20wasn%27t%20a%20choice%20for%20the%20House%20AI%20in%20%22The%20Simpsons%20Treehouse%20of%20Horror%22%20short%2C%20House%20of%20Whacks%3F","correct_answer":"George%20Clooney","incorrect_answers":["Matthew%20Perry","Dennis%20Miller","Pierce%20Brosnan"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"From%20which%20album%20is%20the%20Gorillaz%20song%2C%20%22On%20Melancholy%20Hill%22%20featured%20in%3F","correct_answer":"Plastic%20Beach","incorrect_answers":["Demon%20Days","Humanz","The%20Fall"]},{"category":"General%20Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scotland%20voted%20to%20become%20an%20independent%20country%20during%20the%20referendum%20from%20September%202014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"In%20Left%204%20Dead%2C%20which%20campaign%20has%20the%20protagonists%20going%20through%20a%20subway%20in%20order%20to%20reach%20a%20hospital%20for%20evacuation%3F","correct_answer":"No%20Mercy","incorrect_answers":["Subway%20Sprint","Hospital%20Havoc","Blood%20Harvest"]},{"category":"History","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What%20was%20the%20last%20colony%20the%20UK%20ceded%20marking%20the%20end%20of%20the%20British%20Empire%3F","correct_answer":"Hong%20Kong","incorrect_answers":["India","Australia","Ireland"]}]')}},[[14,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.d83cc6ee.chunk.js.map